[Music]
[音乐]
thank you good morning hi thank you for
谢谢，早上好，谢谢
the introduction yes we're going to talk
简介是的，我们要谈谈
about growl um and we're gonna have very
关于咆哮嗯，我们将有非常
intense 15 minutes here we have lots of
紧张的15分钟，我们这里有很多
content so we're gonna go straight into
内容，所以我们将直接进入
it go fast just like we want our run
就像我们要跑步一样快
times to be fast and starting really
时间要快，真正开始
quick if you have questions but you
如果您有任何问题，请快
don't get time to ask me here and you
没有时间在这里问你
won't find me relator you can find me on
找不到我relator你可以找到我
the Internet
互联网
I almost universally go by Ash life
我几乎都过着灰烬的生活
tweet at me email me find me on github I
给我发推特给我发电子邮件，在github上找到我
can answer questions about software
可以回答有关软件的问题
engineering maybe some gravia unrelated
工程也许有些无关
question and recently I turned 30 so I
问题，最近我30岁了，所以我
feel like I'm old and wise now so I can
觉得我现在已经老了，很聪明，所以我可以
answer questions about life on the rise
回答有关生活在上升的问题
in general as well though please do not
一般也请不要
make any forward going business
做任何向前的业务
decisions based on the contents of what
根据什么内容做出决定
you hear here people say this is a very
你在这里听到人们说这是一个非常
important message so let's go past this
重要信息，让我们越过这一点
and talk about 12m it's very exciting
谈论1200万这是非常令人兴奋的
technology
技术
it's a a smart set high-performance
这是一款高性能的智能套装
polyglot virtual machine capable of
具有以下功能的多语言虚拟机：
running programs in different languages
以不同的语言运行程序
we aim to support all the languages
我们旨在支持所有语言
eventually and currently we have a very
最终，目前我们有一个非常
good set of the most popular ones in the
一组最受欢迎的
ecosystems how many of you have heard of
生态系统你们当中有多少人听说过
bravia just for it quick test excellent
bravia只是为了它快速测试出色
how many of you feel that you can
你们当中有多少人感觉可以
explain and describe what it is and like
解释和描述它是什么和喜欢
why why it exists two hands excellent
为什么为什么存在两只手优秀
have been to my previous sessions we're
去过我以前的课程
gonna ring is that grown vm in one
将会是那个成长中的虚拟机
picture is something like this it's a
图片是这样的
runtime right it's a virtual machine
运行时，它是一个虚拟机
it's a thing that you can execute to run
这是您可以执行运行的东西
your programs you can write them in any
您的程序，您可以用任何方式编写
supported language so currently that is
支持的语言，因此目前
jvm languages Java Scala Kotlin groovy
Java语言Java Scala Kotlin groovy
anything that compiles into the JVM
编译成JVM的任何东西
bytecode goes we have support for
字节码我们支持
JavaScript as a very popular language
JavaScript是一种非常流行的语言
including actually running node.js
包括实际运行的node.js
applications and we have support for
应用程序，我们对
Ruby or Python and anything that goes
Ruby或Python等
the LLVM toolchain right so any native
LLVM工具链正确，因此任何本机
code that compiles through LLVM we can
通过LLVM编译的代码，我们可以
take the intermediate representation the
取中间表示
LLVM bit code and run it and then at
LLVM位代码并运行它，然后在
runtime we try to be a high-performance
运行时，我们努力成为高性能
virtual machine we want to execute the
我们要执行的虚拟机
programs with good peak performance we
程序具有良好的峰值性能，我们
want it to be fast just like probably
希望它像可能的一样快
you want your runtime to be fast life is
您希望您的运行时快生活是
too short to wait for the programs to
太短，无法等待程序执行
finish and then we can execute programs
完成，然后我们可以执行程序
in those languages in different contexts
这些语言在不同的上下文中
we can run it within the JVM and that
我们可以在JVM中运行它
would be like a proper normal Java
就像一个适当的普通Java
process it will start the JVM it will
处理它将启动JVM，它将
normally our build use Java hotspot VM
通常我们的构建使用Java热点VM
so it will it will do everything that
所以它将做所有的事情
Java normally does it will have access
Java通常会访问
to the garbage collection that Java
到Java的垃圾回收
normally does it will lower classes
通常它会降低班级
dynamically it will be your normal
动态地这将是你的正常
perfect Java it can run within the
可以在
context of the node application and that
节点应用程序的上下文
would be normal no the application if
如果没有，将是正常的应用程序
you are interesting those things so it
你对那些事情很感兴趣
will have the event loop it will have
将会有事件循环
the signal handlers that note
注意的信号处理程序
application half it will be just a
应用一半，它只是一个
normal application it's just the engine
正常应用只是引擎
that runs the code within that platform
在该平台上运行代码
is replaced by by our technology and
被我们的技术所取代，
from the very beginning
从一开始就
I think the ground VM project started
我认为地面VM项目已经启动
something like seven years ago and it
大约七年前
started with the idea that maybe we can
开始的想法也许我们可以
write a just-in-time compilers for Java
为Java编写即时编译器
using Java itself right and and from
正确地使用Java本身
that compiler everything else kind of
该编译器的其他一切
followed to what Graham can do now and
接下来是格雷厄姆现在可以做的事情，
from the very beginning the idea was
从一开始的想法是
that we would like a pluggable system
我们想要一个可插拔的系统
that you can embed in in different
你可以嵌入到不同的
scenarios so now you can use the graph
场景，所以现在您可以使用图表
in runtime and put it into your native
在运行时，并将其放入您的本机
or Java applications so if you have a
或Java应用程序，如果您有
large platform and you want to enhance
大型平台，您想增强
it with with the ability to evaluate
具有评估能力
code in in say Java Script or in Python
用Java Script或Python输入代码
you can do that so this way for example
您可以这样做，例如
there are exist some experimental builds
存在一些实验性构建
of Oracle database
Oracle数据库
because Oracle database is a fairly
因为Oracle数据库是一个相当
large native application so there are
大型本机应用程序，所以有
experimental builds where you can use
可在其中使用的实验性构建
ground VM run time to run stored
地面虚拟机运行时间来存储
procedures and usually defined functions
程序和通常定义的功能
using javascript so normally you would
使用JavaScript，所以通常你会
do PL sequel but in those bills you can
做PL续集，但在那些账单中，您可以
use may be easier to understand language
使用可能更容易理解语言
for you
为了你
JavaScript right and the final motor in
JavaScript权利和最终推动力
the in the corner is the standalone
在角落是独立的
applications those are they grow VM
他们成长的应用程序VM
native images which are currently
当前的本机图像
available as an early adopter
可作为早期采用者
technology and this is when we take your
技术，这就是我们采用您的
Java bytecode and we analyze that and we
Java字节码，我们对此进行分析，然后我们
compile it ahead of time to the native
提前将其编译为本机
executable for your platform and the
适用于您的平台和
result it has several advantages it
结果它有几个优点
starts really fast it takes less memory
快速启动，占用更少的内存
at runtime and it's fairly small in size
在运行时，它的体积很小
so there are very useful context where
所以有非常有用的背景
you would like to just concentrate in
你只想专心
that mode but in general growl VM is a
这种模式，但总的来说，咆哮的VM是
large project it can do many many things
大型项目可以做很多事情
it has supports with different languages
它支持不同的语言
I'm sure you can find use cases for
我相信您可以找到以下用例
various scenarios here and the main ones
这里的各种场景和主要场景
that we found by talking to people and
通过与人交谈而发现
by evaluating what they say to us and by
通过评估他们对我们说的话
looking at what they would like to use
看他们想用什么
gravity on for are the following so it's
的重力如下：
a faster runtime it's really a good
更快的运行时间，真的很好
virtual machine right the compiler the
虚拟机对编译器的
just-in-time compiler inside ground vm
地面vm内的即时编译器
is a state of the art well just-in-time
是最先进的技术
compiler so there are many many
编译器，所以有很多很多
workloads where it will give you better
可以为您带来更好工作的工作量
results than other JVM implementations
结果比其他JVM实现
so if you want your a faster runtime for
因此，如果您想更快地运行
you a JVM applications Scala
您一个JVM应用程序Scala
Java coughing and so on then you should
Java咳嗽等等，那么你应该
look at growth em then they grow VM
看着增长，然后他们增长虚拟机
native images they offer you immediate
他们为您提供即时的本地图像
startup for the applications they offer
他们提供的应用程序的启动
you lower footprint if you deploy your
如果部署
applications to the cloud where startup
应用程序启动到云中
and memory consumption are important
和内存消耗很重要
because those are the things you're
因为那些就是你
actually paying for then growl VM native
实际支付然后咆哮的VM本机
images can probably be a solution that
图像可能是一个解决方案
you should at least
你至少应该
look at to see where it works for you
看看它在哪里为您服务
it's an embeddable vm so if you have a
这是一个可嵌入的虚拟机，所以如果您有一个
large application you might want to
您可能想要的大型应用程序
provide the ability to leverage code in
提供利用代码的能力
different languages if you work at a
如果您在
large enterprise by the or even a
大型企业甚至
medium-sized company probably you have
你可能有中型公司
code based in different languages maybe
基于不同语言的代码
you want to run this code within a
您想在一个
single process like spice up your spring
像调味一样的单一过程
application with some machine learning
一些机器学习的应用
bits written in Python because well
用Python写的位，因为
machine learning specialists usually use
机器学习专家通常使用
peyten
皮滕
write for for everything maybe you want
为您可能想要的一切写东西
to run this in a single process or maybe
在单个过程中运行它，或者也许
you just want to write your application
您只想编写您的应用程序
and use the ecosystem from different
并利用不同的生态系统
languages because you just feel like it
语言，因为您只是喜欢
so those are the main values that
所以这些是主要的价值
grapheme can offer you now at least this
字素现在至少可以为您提供
is what we find when talking to people
是我们与人交谈时发现的
who evaluated it and in this session I'm
谁评估了它，在本次会议中，我是
gonna try to go through all of them and
要尝试通过所有这些
quickly explain them and how we achieve
快速解释它们以及我们如何实现
those results and give you more
这些结果，给您更多
information about what happens at the PI
有关PI发生的情况的信息
in the background when dravyam tries to
当dravyam试图在后台
achieve those and of course see some
实现那些，当然看到一些
demos because it's always better to see
演示，因为总能看到更好
things than to hear somebody talking
比听别人说话更重要
about things when you download gravia
下载gravia时的注意事项
you get a following picture it's a it's
您得到以下图片是
a zip archive we're at our archive and
一个zip存档，我们在存档中，
you unzip it and you see this and you
您将其解压缩，然后看到此内容，并且您
can see that this is very similar to the
可以看到，这与
normal jdk distribution that you have
您拥有的正常JDK分布
there are all your normal Java commands
有所有普通的Java命令
there is Java right there in the corner
角落里有Java
Java C Java T and so on so you can use
Java C Java T等，因此您可以使用
it as your just Java Runtime so you can
它只是您的Java Runtime，因此您可以
download it unzip it change your path to
下载它解压缩它更改您的路径
this and and and see whether that brings
这个，然后看看是否带来
you any performance benefits you can
您可以获得任何性能上的好处
also notice that there are more commands
还请注意，还有更多命令
that you typically don't find in the
您通常不会在
Java distribution for example the node
以Java发行版为例
command or for example the ruby or are
命令或例如红宝石或
those who are the launchers for the
那些是发射器的
ground VM to run and start executing
地面虚拟机运行并开始执行
your programs in other languages you
您用其他语言编写的程序
don't necessarily need to
不一定需要
mix all the languages inside a single
将所有语言混合在一起
process you can just execute them
过程中，您可以执行它们
normally so we if you have some code
通常，如果您有一些代码，我们
written in Ruby you just use that Ruby
用Ruby编写，您只需使用Ruby
and it's gonna work hopefully we'll see
希望能成功，我们会看到
right so this is what you get
对，所以这就是你得到的
how do you get that it's fairly simple
你怎么知道这很简单
what would first we start with the
首先从什么开始
architecture what happens when you
建筑，当你
execute our Java command we start the
执行我们的Java命令，我们开始
normal Jamie own process and we built on
正常的杰米自己的过程，我们建立在
the Java hotspot VM and this is a normal
Java热点VM，这是正常现象
gene ium and what we did we replace the
genium，我们做了什么，我们取代了
top tier just-in-time compiler with the
顶级即时编译器
ground vm compiler this is a compiler
地面vm编译器这是一个编译器
written in Java and it uses the JVM shy
用Java编写，并且使用害羞的JVM
interface to integrate with the Virtual
与Virtual集成的界面
Machine JVM Shina interface if you
机器JVM Shina接口，如果您
didn't know is the java virtual machine
不知道是Java虚拟机
compiler in interface da and this is the
接口da中的编译器，这是
interface that you implement when you
您实现时实现的接口
want to supply third-party compiler for
想要提供第三方编译器
JVM it means that it was added to Java 9
JVM意味着它已添加到Java 9中
anything through a Jap 243 and it's it's
通过Jap 243进行的任何操作
in the open JDK and and it's usable
在开放的JDK中，它是可用的
there so through that we integrate draw
在那里，通过整合画图
the EM compiler with the JVM with those
带有JVM的EM编译器
two layers of of the infrastructure for
基础设施的两层
the runtime we can run normal Java
运行时，我们可以运行普通的Java
programs normally right the JVM will
通常在JVM上运行的程序
find your classes it will look at the
找到您的课程，它将查看
byte code it will verify it as the JVM
字节码，它将验证它是否为JVM
normally does it will load started
通常会加载开始吗
tempering and at some point of time it
回火，并在某个时间点
will give the bytecode of the
将给出的字节码
application to the compiler to the
应用到编译器
just-in-time compiler and say please
即时编译器，请说
optimize this for me and then it will
为我优化它，然后它将
receive the machine code and everything
接收机器代码和一切
is going to be splendid and our
将会很棒，而我们
application will suddenly run faster so
应用程序会突然运行得更快，所以
normally normally there will be
通常通常会有
different
不同
top tier compiler if you just download
顶级编译器（如果您只是下载）
open JDK for example and you run you'll
例如打开JDK，然后运行
have C 2 as the most optimizing
使C 2最优化
just-in-time compiler integral VM
即时编译器集成VM
process the top tier compiler is
处理顶级编译器是
replaced by hours CT is still there
由小时数CT替代仍然存在
because
因为
normal JVM so you can disable the
普通的JVM，因此您可以禁用
guavian compiler and run it normally so
危地马拉编译器并正常运行
we just supply additional things to the
我们只是向
Java distribution and that doesn't
Java发行版，那不是
enough and that is fine if you want to
足够，如果您愿意，那很好
run just the jvm languages which most
只运行大多数的jvm语言
probably is what you are the most
大概就是你最
interesting in how many of you write
有趣的是你们写了多少
Java like daily except weekends
爪哇每天都喜欢，周末除外
how many of you use other genome
你们有多少人使用其他基因组
languages
语言
Scala clapping cotton on here is pretty
斯卡拉拍拍棉花在这里很漂亮
good excellent quite quite a bit how
好很好相当如何
many of you run say no js' applications
你们中许多人说没有js的应用程序
surprisingly not very few excellent so
出人意料的是，不是很多优秀的
if you run just JD on languages this is
如果您只在语言上运行JD，这是
enough but if you want support for other
够了，但是如果您想要其他的支持
languages this is typically not enough
语言，这通常是不够的
you want additional support by the
您希望获得其他支持
runtime for the languages one approach
语言的运行时一种方法
that typically people take is to make an
人们通常会采用
optimizing compiler themselves to
优化编译器本身以
translate the structures and code in a
将结构和代码翻译成
high level dynamic language say Java
高级动态语言，说Java
Script to the underlying intermediate
脚本到基础中间件
language say the JVM bytecode they
语言说他们的JVM字节码
manually create this mapping the
手动创建此映射
compiler and then they run bytecode
编译器，然后运行字节码
normally through this this is how I
通常通过这就是我
think masteren worked this is how Jason
认为masteren是这样工作的，Jason就是这样
worked the Python implementation for the
为Python工作
JVM and one thing that those
JVM和那些
implementations have in common is that
实现的共同点是
the maintenance burden is quite high you
您的维护负担很高
have to manually translate high-level
必须手动翻译高级
language into a fairly constrained
语言变成相当有限的
low-level vocabulary of the JVM bytecode
JVM字节码的低级词汇
it is not an easy job and when the
这不是一件容易的事，当
language evolves it's even harder to
语言发展，甚至变得更加困难
maintain this comfortability with
保持这种舒适感
language so since we wanted to support
语言，因为我们想要支持
all the languages it was clearly that we
所有语言显然是我们
need a different approach so we created
需要一种不同的方法，所以我们创建了
a framework called today truffle
今天称为松露的框架
framework it's a framework to create
框架这是一个创建框架
managed languages it's a framework that
托管语言，这是一个框架
offers you an API to describe the
为您提供描述该API的API
semantics of your language so we need to
您语言的语义，因此我们需要
use that API to implement an interpreter
使用该API来实现解释器
for your programming language
用于您的编程语言
implementing interpreters
实施口译员
it's fairly straightforward process
这是一个非常简单的过程
imagine you have a you have a program
想像你有一个程序
you parse that program in the abstract
您以抽象方式解析该程序
syntax tree there are nodes every node
语法树每个节点都有节点
specifies one operation and you just
指定一个操作，您只需
describe the semantics of that operation
描述该操作的语义
in like in the high-level language like
在像高级语言一样
Java so say a JavaScript plus operation
Java，可以说是JavaScript plus操作
will be left operand plus right operand
将是左操作数加右操作数
right you don't have to figure out how
对，您不必弄清楚如何
exactly the conversion rules work you
转换规则确实对您有效
don't have to map that in the low-level
不必在低层映射
byte code language you use a high-level
您使用高级字节码语言
language you describe it you specify a
您描述的语言，您指定了
couple of annotations to hint the
几个注释来提示
truffle framework what to do with this
松露框架怎么办
particular node implementation and then
特定的节点实现，然后
you are done this is something what's
你完成了，这是什么
what people typically did like on the in
人们通常会喜欢什么
the first compiler scores or something
第一个编译器得分或其他
building an interpreter for the language
为语言构建口译员
it's much much smaller effort than
比这要少得多的努力
actually building a runtime or an
实际构建运行时或
optimizing compiler the downside of that
优化编译器的缺点
approach is of course that such
方法当然是这样的
interpreters are inherently slow there
那里的口译员天生就很慢
are slow because they're incredibly
之所以慢，是因为它们令人难以置信
dynamic because every time for every
动态的，因为每次都
operation they have to do an evaluation
操作他们必须做一个评估
of a certain class they need to call a
他们需要打电话给某个班级的
certain method something like my node
某些方法，例如我的节点
evaluate just to figure out every single
评估只是找出每个
operation so if you have liquid small
操作，所以如果您有少量液体
note that adds two integers you need to
请注意，您需要将两个整数相加
have three virtual calls you need to
您需要进行三个虚拟通话
evaluate the left operand the right
评估左边的操作数，右边的
operand and then plus this is gonna be
操作数，然后加上这将是
incredibly slow and we don't want that
太慢了，我们不想要那样
so how truffle deals with that problem
那么松露如何解决这个问题
we we run specialization there we merge
我们在那里运行专业化，我们合并
at runtime we collect the profile and we
在运行时，我们收集配置文件，我们
merge the actual applicant application
合并实际的申请人申请
the program you're running and the code
您正在运行的程序和代码
of the interpreter we inline everything
口译员我们内联了所有内容
and then that code becomes much more
然后该代码变得更多
efficient and then we pass it to the
高效，然后我们将其传递给
ground Veeam compiler and it optimizes
Veeam地面编译器，它进行了优化
it again at a JIT compiler level so
在JIT编译器级别再次
machine code becomes quite an optimized
机器代码变得非常优化
and we get good results performance wise
并且我们在性能方面取得了不错的成绩
for those languages for the native
对于那些母语的人
languages since we cannot run just
语言，因为我们不能只运行
native code in an interpreted mode yet
本机代码处于解释模式
what we
我们做什么
we created an interpreter for the LLVM
我们为LLVM创建了一个解释器
bit code and through that we can run
位代码，通过它我们可以运行
native code and that is used to support
本机代码，用于支持
the native parts native extensions for
本机部分的本机扩展
the dynamic languages that uses them so
使用它们的动态语言
say you run Python for some machine
说你在某些机器上运行Python
learning and then there is a numpy
学习，然后有一个麻木
module which is how you do calculations
模块是您如何计算的
and it has some Python code but it also
它有一些Python代码，但它也
has like quite a large code base written
就像编写了相当大的代码库
name in I think C or C++ right and we
我认为C或C ++正确的名称，我们
want that through LLVM interpreter in
希望通过LLVM解释器
the same process and since all those
相同的过程，因为所有这些
languages they from the point of runtime
他们从运行时的角度
they look the same right they are all
他们看起来都一样，都是
just trees written using the same
只是使用相同的树
framework so from the runtime point of
框架，因此从运行时
view there is no difference whether
查看是否没有区别
you're running code in Python or
您正在使用Python或
JavaScript or Ruby and we can optimize
JavaScript或Ruby，我们可以优化
and compile across the language barrier
并跨越语言障碍进行编译
right so we can inline your native
好的，所以我们可以内联您的母语
extension code into your dynamic
扩展代码进入动态
language code so currently Java and
语言代码，因此目前是Java和
Scala and jvm languages are a little bit
Scala和jvm语言有点
different there is a more intricate
不同的是更复杂
Interop protocol needed between the jvm
jvm之间需要Interop协议
languages and others but eventually we
语言和其他语言，但最终我们
will get them to be implemented on the
将使它们在
truffle framework as well and then they
松露框架，然后他们
will be absolutely equal in all three
在这三个方面将绝对相等
arts right so this is how it looks when
没错，这就是它的外观
you run these things how you can run
您运行这些东西如何运行
these things is it's an open source
这些东西是开源的
project
项目
Grahame is an open source it sits on
Grahame是它的开源软件
github you can go there it's written
github你可以去那里写
largely in Java so as Java developers I
很大程度上是用Java开发的
feel that we can appreciate this you can
觉得我们可以体会到这一点
load that into your ID your normal
正常加载到您的ID
tooling will work you don't need to
工具将使您不需要
figure out intricate ways to compile
找出复杂的编译方式
that it just you understand how the code
只是您了解代码
works you can go click through the class
您可以点击该课程的作品
definitions and feel like you understand
定义和感觉像您了解
what is happening it still takes a
发生了什么仍然需要
little bit of experience and an
一点经验和
understanding to you I don't know some
了解你，我不知道
bit patches and contribute in that way
一点补丁，并以此方式做出贡献
because it is still a compiler
因为它仍然是编译器
engineering so
工程如此
at least I think I think on average
至少我认为我平均而言
you'd need to put in at least one
您需要至少放入一个
weekend before you start contributing
开始贡献之前的周末
probably more but it's written in Java
可能更多，但这是用Java编写的
and you can understand what is doing and
您可以了解正在做什么，
you can see and if there are any errors
您可以查看是否有任何错误
you get properly normal exceptions
你会得到正常的正常例外
instead of the seg faults and and it's
而不是段错误，这是
much easier to work with and you can
更容易使用，您可以
build it yourself you can you can
自己建造它，你可以
package it you get a fully functional
打包就可以了
random distribution you also don't have
您也没有随机分布
to because you can just use our binaries
因为您只能使用我们的二进制文件
so the team provides builds that he can
因此团队可以提供他可以
use just those zip archives that you can
仅使用您可以使用的那些zip存档
unpack there was the Community Edition
解压那里是社区版
which is the artifact that you get when
这是当你得到的神器
you build the open-source bit and it's
您构建了开放源代码，
really great
非常好
it has good performance it is fully
它具有良好的性能，它是完全
functional it will run all programs that
功能将运行所有程序
grapheme can run and also there is an
字素可以运行，并且还有一个
Enterprise Edition which is a
企业版是
proprietary product at Oracle and it
Oracle及其专有产品
comes with even better performance so
具有更好的性能，所以
the compiler is optimized more there are
编译器经过优化，有更多
more compiler phases and passes that it
更多的编译器阶段并通过它
will do it will spend a little more time
会花更多的时间
trying to optimize code but typically it
尝试优化代码，但通常是
will give you even better result at
将为您带来更好的结果
performance so currently we have Linux
性能，所以目前我们有Linux
and Mac OS as support the platforms for
和Mac OS作为支持平台
the binaries we have an experimental
我们有一个实验性的二进制文件
Windows built that that can do certain
Windows内置的功能可以做到
things so we can experiment with that
事情，所以我们可以尝试一下
but mostly we have the binaries for
但大多数情况下，我们有用于
linux's and Mac's which is good because
linux和Mac的好，因为
production typically runs on Linux so we
生产通常在Linux上运行，因此我们
can get those one point which is I'm
可以得到我的那一点
very excited about this that earlier
早些时候对此感到非常兴奋
this month we launched grow vm 19.0 and
本月，我们推出了成长虚拟机19.0和
together was at work a launch dravyam
一起在工作中的发射dravyam
oracle grave IAM enterprise as a product
甲骨文IAM企业级产品
that means that worker will provide
这意味着工人将提供
support for it that means that if you
支持它，这意味着如果您
want to use you can you can turn to an
想用你可以的你可以转向
oracle representative and talk about
甲骨文代表和谈
that and that also means that the
那也意味着
project has really good chances at being
这个项目真的有很好的机会
in life for a very long period of time
生活很长一段时间
so you can look into that if you will if
所以你可以调查一下
you want
你要
but the Community Edition is fully
但是社区版完全
functional and you can run it and if you
功能，您可以运行它，如果您
just want additional performance you can
只想要额外的性能就可以
figure it out later
以后再弄清楚
with that let's go and let's see some
一起走吧，让我们看一些
demos and let's see what what
演示，让我们看看
performance impact I'm talking about
我正在谈论的性能影响
let's see I have this very simple
让我们看看我有这么简单
benchmark and normally I show a little
基准，通常我会显示一些
bit different one also synthetic but
有点不同也可以合成
since we are at the Spring Conference
因为我们在 Spring 会议上
here I have felt that I should I should
在这里，我觉得我应该
run a small benchmark using the project
使用项目运行一个小型基准
reactor API to benchmark it a little bit
反应器API对其进行基准测试
so let me show you how to run it and
所以让我告诉你如何运行它，
then we'll stare at the code a little
然后我们会稍微看一下代码
bit more right what did I do
正确一点，我做了什么
I download my Graham I have my utilities
我下载我的Graham我有我的工具
and commands here which if I call which
和命令在这里，如果我叫哪个
Java you can see that this is my Java
Java您可以看到这是我的Java
from the ground vm distribution if I
从地面vm分发，如果我
call Java - version you can see that
调用Java-您可以看到的版本
this is a built based on Java 8 right so
这是基于Java 8构建的，所以
when I when I run my Java commands this
当我运行Java命令时
is this Java is in my path all the time
这个Java一直在我的路上吗
right when I run anything Java this is
正确，当我运行任何Java时，这是
what runs which should give you enough
运行什么应该给你足够的
confidence to just drop it into
有信心放进去
production without any regard for do you
生产不考虑你
process because I run it in my laptop no
的过程，因为我在笔记本电脑上运行它
you should evaluate but you should know
你应该评估，但你应该知道
that we run our internal Java
我们运行内部Java
applications at Oracle apps on the
Oracle应用程序上的应用程序
ground VM and we we don't see we don't
地面虚拟机，我们看不到
see many problems right what do I want
看到很多问题，我想要什么
to do I want you to run the benchmark
我要您运行基准测试
for you right so I will I will run the
为您服务，所以我将运行
following file I will run without the
以下文件我将在没有
groundhog compiler first to show you the
土拨鼠编译器首先向您展示
difference right I will run my java from
差异对吧，我将从
the ground vm but i will disable the JVM
地面虚拟机，但我将禁用JVM
so I compiler right this is what I meant
所以我编译对，这就是我的意思
when it said that you can run your drama
当它说你可以演戏
absolutely normally I can disable the
绝对正常，我可以禁用
compiler I can just say do not use the
编译器我只能说不要使用
grant compiler
授权编译器
and it will run properly anyway right so
而且它将正常运行，所以
I will start it we do not use the JVM
我将开始它，我们不使用JVM
state compiler it will take 40 seconds
状态编译器将花费40秒
and will see the results in 4 seconds
并在4秒内看到结果
let's look at the code what does it do
让我们看一下代码是做什么的
it takes some array of of objects
它需要一些对象
integers in this case and then it has
在这种情况下的整数，然后有
one test method for which we we check
我们检查的一种测试方法
the latency so lower results will be
延迟，因此较低的结果将是
better the average time to execute this
更好的平均执行时间
method and what we just do we stream
方法以及我们所做的事情
those values we apply some
这些价值观，我们适用一些
transformation to them we reduce them to
转化为他们，我们将它们减少为
a number and we just collect this
一个数字，我们只是收集这个
pipeline with a block right this may be
带有块的管道可能是
not the code that you write daily like
而不是您每天编写的代码
unless you're writing applications that
除非您编写的应用程序
transform like a hundred integers but
像一百个整数一样转换
this MZ trains certain pad code pass in
这个MZ训练某些密码通过
the framework that powers actually the
实际上为
whole reactive reactive string story
整个电抗弦乐
project or actor issue which is which is
项目或演员的问题是
yeast when you run your spring
Spring 跑步时酵母
applications and one of this benchmark
应用程序和该基准之一
is clearly synthetic you at least know
至少是合成的，至少你知道
that it actually uses the code that you
它实际上使用了您的代码
also use in production hopefully 40
也可用于生产40
seconds has passed right so we get the
秒过去了，所以我们得到了
number and it's a fairly large number
数字，这是一个相当大的数字
because it needs to go through all
因为它需要经历所有
hundred elements and it needs to create
一百个元素，它需要创建
a subscription subscriber and all those
订阅订户以及所有这些
elements and push the data through this
元素并通过它推送数据
pipeline so we get something like
管道，所以我们得到像
twenty-four hundred nanoseconds per
每秒24400纳秒
operation so now I will do and I will
操作，所以现在我会做，我会
run the version without disabling the
运行版本而不禁用
Grove am compiler right so with our Java
Grove am编译器正确，因此使用我们的Java
which you get from the ground game
你从地面游戏中得到的
distribution the ground VM compiler is
分发地面VM编译器
enabled by default so now I will not
默认情况下启用，所以现在我不会
disable this manually and I will run it
手动禁用它，我将运行它
and we'll see the results not to spoil
我们会看到结果不会变质
the results we'll stir the benchmark a
结果，我们将搅动基准
little bit more right who thinks it
多一点正确的人认为
would be faster show of hands
会更快地举手
I understand your skepticism JVM is a
我了解您的怀疑态度JVM是
state-of-the-art virtual machine it's
最先进的虚拟机
not easy to be faster than the JDM but
要比JDM更快并不容易，但是
hopefully it will be faster because this
希望它会更快，因为这
is the demo and it would be silly to
是演示，这将是愚蠢的
show you the benchmark where we're
向您展示我们的基准
slower but honestly I normally on the
慢一点，但老实说我通常在
stage do a different one so I really
舞台做一个不同的，所以我真的
come in a little bit nervous I'm fairly
有点紧张我很公平
capable sure that this will be
有能力确保这将是
but we'll see the results how much
但我们会看到结果多少
faster do you think who thinks it will
您认为谁会更快
be faster at 10% or more okay
更快达到10％或更多可以
fairly enough optimistic people twenty
相当乐观的人二十
percent or more that's a lot right ten
百分之十或更多十
percent on the JVM kind of can buy you
百分比的JVM可以买到你
like a low latency garbage collector
像低延迟的垃圾收集器
when the introduced do you want to see I
什么时候介绍你想看我
think the the the idea was that 10%
认为这个想法是10％
throughput decrease is at most what you
吞吐量下降最多就是你
will receive when you run to say which
当您说出哪个会收到
do you want you see and I think other
你想看到吗，我想其他
low latency garbage collectors also try
低延迟垃圾收集器也尝试
to have this overhead no more than 10
这样的开销不超过10
percent so 10 percent by city low
％，按城市低位计算，为10％
latency GC 20 percent buys you low
延迟20％的GC会让您觉得便宜
latency GCS and a little bit more
延迟GCS等
anything else is a gravy right anything
其他任何东西都是肉汁吧
else you get is what you save in pure
否则，你得到的就是你纯粹保存的东西
money if you run say on some cloud where
钱，如果你在某个云上说
you pay for compute instances so let's
您为计算实例付费，所以让我们
see and let's see how fast is this or
看，让我们看看这有多快
how slow this oh look at that
哦，看它有多慢
the score for running one iteration of
运行一次迭代的分数
this test method is 89 seconds 1824
这个测试方法是89秒1824
2,580
2,580
my mass is not good but if you divide
我的质量不好，但如果你分裂
that that is 30 times so with the
那是30倍
growing vm compiler enabled this
不断增长的vm编译器启用了此功能
benchmark is 30 times faster than
基准比30倍快
normally that is an amazing result that
通常那是一个惊人的结果
there's also clearly not representative
显然也没有代表性
of were all workloads that you're gonna
都是您要承担的工作量
run so if you run the application I
运行，所以如果您运行应用程序我
don't think you will see the 30 percent
不要以为你会看到百分之三十
three times performance boost this is
性能提升三倍，这是
just ridiculous to expect that and it's
只是荒谬的期望，这是
a it's a it's a benchmark shown on stage
这是舞台上显示的基准
so you should take that result with a
所以你应该用一个
grain of salt because we run this on my
一粒盐，因为我们在我的
poor macbook here which is clearly not
可怜的MacBook在这里，这显然不是
the most scientific benchmarking
最科学的基准
environment so you should you should you
环境，所以你应该你应该
should not trust this number you can
不应该相信这个号码
even see that the numbers below are just
甚至看到下面的数字仅仅是
data you have to interpret them in a
数据，您必须将其解释为
meaningful and reasonable way
有意义和合理的方式
you have to understand what's happening
你必须了解发生了什么
so this is the pessimistic view on this
所以这是悲观的观点
raft the optimistic view in this result
在这个结果中泛泛乐观的看法
and this is what I want you to you do
这就是我想要你做的
you understand from this number it that
从这个数字你知道
is possible that programs written in
编写的程序是否可能
Java running on the JVM will be
在JVM上运行的Java将
significantly faster if you run them on
如果在它们上运行，速度会大大提高
the ground VM
地面虚拟机
right it doesn't have to be like three
对，不必像三个
times faster but even if you get a 20%
快一倍，但即使您得到20％
performance boost that is a lot right so
性能提升非常正确，因此
if this doesn't convince you to at least
如果这至少不能说服您
evaluate probiem then i'm gonna show you
评估能力，然后我会告诉你
more slides about this i want to say
我想说更多有关此的幻灯片
nothing willed but actually maybe some
什么都不愿意，但实际上也许有些
other things well alright so internally
其他事情很好，所以在内部
we're on tons of benchmarks and we get
我们有大量的基准，我们得到
the results one benchmark seed that we
结果是我们的基准种子
recently published big by we I mean the
最近出版的大书，我的意思是
engineers who actually do performance
实际执行性能的工程师
was the Renaissance it what we wanted to
是我们想要的文艺复兴时期
do is that is to gather the stern number
这样做是为了收集船尾号
of use cases which represent modern Java
代表现代Java的用例
right so normal benchmarks we run the
是的，所以我们运行正常的基准测试
coppice we run the spec JVM spec jbb all
我们运行规范JVM规范jbb all
of those we see those numbers but we
其中我们看到了这些数字，但我们
often feel that they're maybe not the
常常觉得他们可能不是
most representative of the modern
现代最有代表性的
workloads how many of you like right
你有多少人喜欢正确的工作量
fractals for living how many of you deal
分形为生活多少人
low level math clearly that code gets
低级数学显然可以得到代码
running right because that's what we
运行正确，因为这就是我们
build on as a foundation it's running in
在它运行的基础上建立
the infrastructure is the code like that
基础架构就是这样的代码
is running in the JVM itself in the JDK
在JDK的JVM本身中运行
standard of library but maybe maybe we
图书馆的标准，但也许我们
just use the higher-level libraries
只需使用更高级别的库
maybe we use some reactive code maybe we
也许我们使用一些反应式代码，也许我们
use some reactive extensions maybe we
使用一些反应性扩展，也许我们
use some akka maybe we do some Bayesian
用一些阿卡也许我们做一些贝叶斯
reasoning sir right maybe we do some
先生，也许我们可以做点什么
newer for J maybe we run with workloads
对于J而言较新，也许我们需要处理工作负载
where the tons of objects in memory and
内存中有大量物体
they are they are they are just sitting
他们是他们是他们只是坐在
there and the compiler needs different
那里和编译器需要不同
set of optimizations to show good
一组优化以显示良好
performance and O's so we looked at
性能和O，所以我们研究了
those numbers and with
这些数字和
that the the Renaissance benchmark seat
文艺复兴时期的基准座位
represents modern workloads quite well
很好地代表了现代工作量
so the important bit here is to notice
所以这里重要的一点是要注意
that the gravity I'm Community Edition
我是社区版的引力
is a little bit volatile quite often is
经常有点不稳定
it is faster than openjdk sometimes it's
它比openjdk更快，有时
a little bit slower we run many many
慢一点，我们跑很多
benchmarks we if we collapse that to a
基准，如果我们将其折叠成一个
single number Grand Am Community Edition
单号Grand Am Community Edition
comes approximately one percent faster
快约百分之一
than open JDK right so that's an average
比打开JDK好，这是一个平均水平
temperature in the hospital that number
那个医院的温度那个数字
tells you nothing you have to clearly
告诉你什么都不需要你清楚
evaluate that on your workload on your
评估您的工作量
hardware on your application code
您的应用程序代码上的硬件
patterns and what we see there is very
模式和我们看到的非常
often it gives you good performance
通常它会给你很好的表现
boost over open JDK so if you understand
提高开放的JDK，所以如果您了解
what you're doing if you understand the
如果您了解
performance patterns of your application
应用程序的性能模式
you are welcome to use the Community
欢迎您使用社区
Edition and it will probably give you
版，它可能会给你
quite a performance boost the Enterprise
相当大的性能提升了企业
Edition of course being a product
当然是产品的版本
probably gives you a much more a better
可能会给你带来更好的效果
performance boost and it's universally
性能提升，并且普遍存在
faster than open JDK so if you don't
比打开JDK更快，所以如果您不这样做
know anything about performance you can
对性能一无所知
you can look into getting that we run
您可以调查一下我们的运行情况
other benchmarks as well and we often
其他基准，我们经常
blog about what what happens beside
关于旁边发生了什么的博客
behind the scenes with the ground VM so
与地面虚拟机一起在幕后
we if you use Java 8 and later how many
我们如果您使用Java 8及更高版本
of you use run Java it's in production
您使用运行Java在生产中
very nice almost always everyone how
几乎每个人都非常好
many of you run Java 9 plus not bad I
你们中的许多人都运行Java 9，而且还不错
think this is the largest percentage
认为这是最大的百分比
they've seen from the sessions very good
他们从会议上看到非常好
you are very up to date with the common
你非常了解普通人
modern Java so if you run those modern
现代Java，因此，如果您运行那些现代
Chaves you probably use lambdas
你可能会使用lambdas
everywhere you probably you stream API
您可能在任何地方流式传输API
so you try to use maybe immutable data
所以你尝试使用也许不变的数据
structures on those code patterns we
这些代码模式的结构
should really go to performance boost
应该真正提高性能
you can read about that in at medium.com
您可以在medium.com上了解到
slash ground um we show really good
斜线嗯，我们表现得很好
numbers for scholar because Scala
学者的数字，因为斯卡拉
bytecode patterns are a little bit
字节码模式有点
different from the normal bytecode
与普通字节码不同
patterns that Java programs create
Java程序创建的模式
because unity translates like a higher
因为团结翻译得更高
level at
的水平
structions to the bytecode so they they
字节码的指令，所以它们
do it a little bit differently and we
有所不同，我们
show really good results on Scala but we
在Scala上显示出非常好的结果，但是我们
also we also are trying to be a good
我们也想成为一个好人
open source project so now in the ground
开源项目，所以现在在地下
VM we have the open JDK the Java hotspot
VM我们有开放的JDK Java热点
vm implementation and open JDK projects
vm实施和打开JDK项目
take the gray vm compiler and they pull
用灰色的vm编译器，他们拉
it into their sources because well open
它进入他们的资源，因为它很开放
source and they package it so if you run
源并将其打包，因此如果您运行
java I think ten plus maybe nine as well
Java我认为十加九
what you can do you can enable certain
你可以做什么，你可以启用某些
common line parameters some options and
公用线路参数一些选项和
you can get the version of the grand-am
你可以得到爷爷的版本
compiler inside the open JDK right and
打开JDK里面的编译器，然后
you don't need to download anything else
您不需要下载其他任何内容
and that would be the open source
那将是开源的
version of the compiler it probably not
版本的编译器可能没有
be like latest and greatest for the
像最新的和最伟大的
ground from the gray layer master but it
从灰色层主控器接地，但它
will be one when they pulled these
当他们拉这些将是一个
sources into the open JDK forest when
来源进入开放式JDK林时
they patched it so to get that you need
他们打了补丁，以便您需要
to unlock experimental vm options and
解锁实验机选项
use JVM Sai compiler and with those you
使用JVM Sai编译器，并与您一起使用
are gonna be running the Grand Am
将会经营Grand Am
compiler and you're gonna be
编译器，您将成为
experiencing different performance
经历不同的表现
patterns in your application if you're
您的应用程序中的模式
asking how good that is
问那有多好
it depends on the workload so we the
这取决于工作量，所以我们
remember of benchmarks where we should
记住基准应该在哪里
really get results one of them was this
真正获得结果的其中之一是
appropriate benchmark which which people
哪个人合适基准
show when they want to explain what
当他们想解释什么时显示
values the value types will bring you so
值值类型将为您带来
it's a benchmark where you multiply
这是您倍增的基准
matrices and of complex numbers a
矩阵和复数a
complex number is a number consisting of
复数是一个数字，由
two parts right there are two doubles
两个部分有两个双打
inside it and in this particular
在里面，特别是
benchmark the complex number is
基准复数是
implemented as an immutable data
实现为不可变数据
structure which is very good because as
结构很好，因为
developers this is what we want we want
开发人员这就是我们想要的
programs that they are easy to reason
他们容易推理的程序
about that are easy to debug and
关于这很容易调试和
immutable data structures very often
不可变的数据结构经常
offer us exactly that it's very hard to
确切地告诉我们这很难
figure out what mutates global state but
弄清楚什么会改变全球状态，但是
immutable data structures are
不变的数据结构是
good for reasoning and understanding
善于推理和理解
what they're bad at is that any
他们不擅长的是
operation with the immutable data
不变数据的操作
structures which normally create new
通常会创建新结构的结构
objects right when we do any mobile when
当我们做任何移动时对象正确
we do any well any math operations there
我们在那里做任何数学运算都很好
right we create new objects all the time
对，我们一直在创建新对象
so grandi I'm compiler comes with a
所以格兰迪我是编译器
really good escape analysis and it can
真正好的逃脱分析，它可以
eliminate almost all those allocations
消除几乎所有这些分配
much better than CT good so when we run
比CT好很多，所以当我们跑步时
this on jdk 11 again on this poor
在jdk 11上再次在这个穷人身上
macbook don't trust those numbers but
Macbook不相信这些数字，但是
you can trust the difference in those we
您可以相信我们之间的差异
get with the ground vm compiler from
从地面获得vm编译器
open JDK we get approximately 2x
打开JDK，我们得到大约2倍
speed-up again that won't be your
再次提速那将不是你的
typical speed up on any normal
任何正常速度下的典型速度
application but this is something to
应用程序，但这是要
look into the Enterprise Edition is
看看企业版是
still a little bit faster but the
还是快一点，但是
grand-am Community Edition is really
大am社区版真的
really good too so you can you can you
真的也很好，所以你可以你可以
should look into that right Twitter is
应该研究一下正确的Twitter是
one company that is using the ground
一家正在使用地面的公司
viim compiler the run there's two common
viim编译器的运行有两种常见
microservices they travel around the
他们在各地旅行的微服务
world and talk about that because they
世界，谈论这件事，因为他们
want you to run the ground am compiler
希望您运行编译器
as well because that means the compiler
也因为这意味着编译器
will make sure much faster right if more
将确保更快，如果更多
people run their code we using this
人们运行他们的代码，我们使用这个
technology the more stable and mature it
技术越稳定，越成熟
will become so for some time now they
他们会变得如此一段时间
don't have any bugs to report to us so i
没有任何错误可以报告给我们，所以我
think they're fairly happy and what they
认为他们还算幸福，他们
show they show reduction both in the cpu
显示它们在cpu中都显示减少
user time and they show reduction in the
用户时间，并且显示出
latencies because with the better escape
延迟，因为逃脱更好
analysis their programs do not allocate
分析他们的程序没有分配
as much data so they do not pressure the
尽可能多的数据，因此它们不会给
garbage collector there are some new
垃圾收集器有一些新的
developments which we put into the
我们投入的发展
recently announced the ground am 19 one
最近宣布地面上午19一
thing is that we compiled the gravity M
事情是，我们编译了重力M
compiler with the grand-am compiler to
编译器与grand-am编译器一起使用
get the shirt library code before it was
在获得衬衫库代码之前
a jar file and it had to be compiled at
一个jar文件，它必须在以下位置编译
runtime and it's pressured certain parts
运行时，它给某些部分施加压力
of the JDM infrastructure as like it
像这样的JDM基础架构
needed to compile itself and that wasn't
需要自己编译，这不是
super fast to warm up so now it's
超快速热身，所以现在
precompiled machine code and it will
预编译的机器代码，它将
warm up immediately fast and it should
立即快速预热，应该
exhibit all the runtime characteristics
展现所有运行时特征
of normal JDM with CT it just probably
CT的普通JDM
the resulting code could be faster woof
结果代码可能更快
let's talk about polygons really really
让我们真正地谈论多边形
fast because I want to get to the next
快，因为我想到达下一个
topic and there are not super minute
话题，没有超级分钟
much time right let me show you an
好多时间，让我告诉你
example of a spring application where we
Spring 应用的例子
evaluate code in our this is the code in
评估我们的代码，这是其中的代码
our if you're not an art developer you
如果您不是艺术开发商，那么我们
can see this is clearly foreign syntax
可以看到这显然是外国语法
for you this is what you get when you
对你来说，这就是你得到的
get an average Java developer write code
让普通的Java开发人员编写代码
in are probably the most not the most
最可能不是最
idiotic but this is a functional our
愚蠢的，但这是我们的功能
code what we have here is a typical
代码我们这里有一个典型的
string boot application right it starts
字符串启动应用程序启动
it registers some beans and I'm gonna
它注册了一些beans，我要
run it we really hope is not gonna crash
运行它，我们真的希望不会崩溃
right I run this the important bits what
对，我运行这个重要的位子
we see here is that we create a bean
我们看到这里是我们创建一个bean
called contacts and this comes from the
称为联系人，这来自
ground iam API ground iam offers API for
地面iam API地面iam提供API
creating polyglot applications and we
创建多语言应用程序，我们
need to build a context to evaluate
需要建立一个环境来评估
scripts in other languages within it
其中的其他语言的脚本
then we evaluate the source which comes
然后我们评估来源
from just a file property and we get
从一个文件属性，我们得到
that source via valid that and then we
通过有效的那个来源，然后我们
convert that to Java function there is a
将其转换为Java函数
certain API to do normal things
某些API做正常的事情
conversions like integers to integers
像整数到整数的转换
strings to strings collections to
字符串到字符串集合
collections we try to provide a
我们尝试提供的收藏
reasonable abstraction to make
做出合理的抽象
interoperability between languages
语言之间的互操作性
unified across different languages and
跨不同语言统一
also well reasonably enough to work with
也足够合理地与之合作
so here we know that this script this
所以在这里我们知道这个脚本
file gives us just one function so we
文件只给我们一个功能，所以我们
can easily just convert that to a
可以轻松地将其转换为
function which is what what'swhat's that
那是什么功能
function this is Java util function
函数这是Java util函数
function
功能
it's not even our API anymore right this
这甚至不是我们的API了
is your normal Java the best thing is
是您的普通Java最好的是
after that we just use that normally we
在那之后，我们通常使用
pass Java objects to it right which wrap
将Java对象正确传递给它
Java primitive values we apply that we
我们应用Java基本值
get
得到
result which is a Java string and we
结果是一个Java字符串，我们
just render that string on screen so
只需在屏幕上呈现该字符串，
let's see if it started yeah I think it
让我们看看它是否开始是的，我认为
started it started localhost:8080 load
启动它启动了localhost：8080加载
right we see whether it works not what
对，我们看看它是否有效
this application does it does nothing it
该应用程序不执行任何操作
passed random data some system load
通过随机数据一些系统负载
average to the our code and it used the
平均到我们的代码，它使用了
our facilities to plot that code to an
我们的设施将代码绘制到
SVG image not the most exciting may be
SVG图像可能不是最令人兴奋的
example but you can see it clear the
示例，但您可以看到它清除了
words and it loads initially a little
单词，它最初会加载一点
bit slower because it needs to load
慢一点，因为它需要加载
their standard of library and it needs
他们的图书馆标准和需要
to compile the code so it needs to
编译代码，因此需要
gather the profile but then it gets
收集个人资料，但随后得到
really bit faster and faster so the data
真的越来越快，所以数据
goes from Java normal Java objects to
从Java普通Java对象到
our our code there is no conversion or
我们的代码没有转换或
serialization happening it's in the same
序列化发生在同一
process and then inside our code this is
过程，然后在我们的代码中，这是
fairly interesting we can use that when
相当有趣，我们可以在
I say our code this could be any
我说我们的代码可以是任何
language that we support it could be
我们支持的语言可能是
JavaScript Python Ruby R or anything
JavaScript Python Ruby R或其他任何东西
native right we can use Java types and
我们可以使用Java类型
and use them normally so here we will
并正常使用它们，所以在这里我们将
have the logger and we'll log some data
有记录器，我们将记录一些数据
both the Jama values and some data in
Jama值和其中的一些数据
there are internal type numeric right
有内部类型数字的权利
and you can see they are logging the and
您会看到他们正在记录和
they're logging normally without any
他们通常没有任何记录
conversions and if you actually if we
转化，如果您实际上是否
look here right this method has a
看看这里，这个方法有一个
signature of double and an array of
double的签名和一个数组
doubles so we don't even convert like
加倍，所以我们甚至都不会像
two objects and then do casts right you
两个物体然后对你施展
can use your code normally you can offer
可以正常使用您可以提供的代码
you Java code to programs in other
您的Java代码到其他程序
languages and you can use programs it
语言，您可以使用程序
now to other languages inside your Java
现在到Java中的其他语言
code normally isn't this amazing
代码通常不是那么神奇
I will stop this and then we'll quickly
我会停止这个，然后我们会尽快
go back and show a couple of slides
回去展示几张幻灯片
about this right our JavaScript
关于这个权利我们的JavaScript
compatibilities of the charts if you
图表的兼容性，如果您
follow modern JavaScript development
跟随现代JavaScript开发
there are standards right the language
语言有标准
evolves so we are at the computability
不断发展，因此我们处于可计算性
levels similar to normal note similar to
类似于普通音符的水平
the browsers
浏览器
including the upcoming equus trip 2019
包括即将到来的2019马术之旅
draft it's not even started but we are
起草还没有开始，但是我们
compatible because we don't need to
兼容，因为我们不需要
manually translate javascript to
手动将javascript转换为
bytecode and we just need an interpreter
字节码，我们只需要一个解释器
our javascript is super fast it's much
我们的javascript超级快
faster than than previously being
比以前更快
possible to evaluate JavaScript on the
可以在
JVM if you used an aspirin for example
JVM（例如，如果您使用阿司匹林）
our javascript is actually a little bit
我们的JavaScript实际上是一点
slower than v8 at peak performance this
在峰值性能下比v8慢
is a shame but we'll get there the
很遗憾，但我们会到达那里
problem team is committed to make gravia
问题团队致力于做gravia
the best run time in class for all
所有班级中最佳的运行时间
supported languages so we want to be the
支持的语言，因此我们希望成为
fastest ruby the fastest python the
最快的红宝石最快的python
fastest run time for the jvm languages
jvm语言最快的运行时间
and so on you can also use that as just
等等，您也可以将其用作
a collection of Java jar files and plug
Java jar文件和插件的集合
them into your normal open JDK process
将它们放入正常的开放JDK流程中
to be honest the languages foreground
老实说语言前景
Liam will run the best in the presence
利亚姆会在场上表现最好
of the ground vm compiler the truffle
地面vm编译器的松露
runtime needs certain things from the
运行时需要从
from the compiler certain intrinsics and
来自编译器的某些内在函数和
certain optimizations which grand-am
某些优化，其中
compiler accidentally offers surprise
编译器意外提供了惊喜
surprise and other compilers do not
惊喜和其他编译器没有
offer but they can write and and other
提供，但他们可以写和其他
JVM scoot offer the JVM Sai interface
JVM scoot提供JVM Sai接口
maybe and they would be able to work
也许，他们将能够工作
with the ground compiler so you can run
与地面编译器，以便您可以运行
growl VMs JavaScript engine on the
咆哮VMs JavaScript引擎
normal JDK without any problems other
普通的JDK没有其他问题
languages I think there are some native
我认为有些本地语言
parts which might not run very well in
可能无法很好运行的零件
this setting yet but we are in different
这个设置还可以，但是我们不同
stages of compatibility anyway our Ruby
Ruby的兼容阶段
is fast and we are as fast our Python is
快，我们的Python快
the youngest so probably it's not yet
最年轻，所以可能还没有
very fast yet and we're working mostly
速度非常快，我们大部分时间都在工作
on the compatibility with the echo
关于回声的兼容性
system specifically to run the machine
系统专门用于运行机器
learning for workloads I know that there
学习工作量我知道
exists a developer's machine where there
那里有一个开发商的机器
are certain patched versions of our
是我们的某些补丁版本
Python implementation and numpy where
Python实现和numpy在哪里
certain numpy workloads actually work so
某些特定的工作量实际上可以正常工作
we are making progress there but if you
我们正在那里取得进展，但是如果您
want to try our Python
想尝试我们的Python
please go with your eyes open and keep
请睁开眼睛，保持
your expectations to a reasonable level
您的期望达到合理水平
I don't want to tell you that our patent
我不想告诉你我们的专利
is amazing and then you will try it and
很棒，然后您将尝试
get discouraged and will never try it
灰心丧气，永远不会尝试
again try it but promise me to try it
再次尝试，但答应我尝试
again next year as well oh the good bet
明年再来一次哦，好赌
you get the tooling since everything to
您将获得所需的工具，因为一切
us is just trees you get the tools that
我们只是树木，您可以获得
can work with old languages right you
可以使用旧语言
don't need to have special developer
不需要特别的开发人员
tooling for any particular language
任何特定语言的工具
because to the runtime to the platform
因为到平台的运行时
all of them are just interpreters
他们都只是口译员
written using the same API so what you
使用相同的API编写的
can get you can get the debugger you can
可以得到你可以得到调试器
get the profiler you can get the heat
得到探查器，你可以得到热量
viewer for free for a language so you
查看器免费提供一种语言，因此您
can use for example chrome inspector in
可以在中使用例如chrome inspector
the browser to debug Ruby or Python you
在浏览器中调试Ruby或Python
can use je visual VM to figure out what
可以使用je visual VM找出什么
happens with your Python application
发生在您的Python应用程序中
what what allocates memory or JavaScript
什么分配内存或JavaScript
application you can use a sampler to
应用程序，您可以使用采样器
figure out what takes time in your in
弄清楚你需要什么时间
your languages in your programs and all
您的程序和所有语言
of those get to you just by implementing
这些只是通过实施而获得
the language on top of the ground
地面上的语言
practice system so that was the polyglot
练习系统，所以这是多语种
3 I am looking forward to hearing people
3我期待听到人们的声音
trying that more and coming to us and
尝试更多，并找到我们
telling us what to improve but let's
告诉我们需要改进的地方，但让我们
talk about the Gran va native images
谈论格兰维亚本地形象
the elephant in the room of the Java
爪哇人房间里的大象
ecosystem lately a very hot topic
生态系统最近是一个非常热门的话题
growing native images available as an
越来越多的本机图像可作为
early adopter technology what it does it
早期采用者技术的作用
can compile your application ahead of
可以提前编译您的应用程序
time to the native binary what you get
时间到本地二进制文件你会得到什么
is the fully compiled blob native of my
是我的完全编译的Blob本机
native code right you get one file that
本机代码正确，您得到一个文件
is has no dependencies OGG them it will
没有依赖OGG他们会
still run your application it will still
仍然运行您的应用程序，它将仍然
run with certain components of a virtual
与虚拟的某些组件一起运行
machine that you would expect right you
您期望正确的机器
write your programs and you expect the
写你的程序，你期望
runtime to provide you with a garbage
运行时为您提供垃圾
collector you expect that your program
收藏家，您希望您的程序
will work as if memmer was infinite so
会像记忆无限一样工作
what you get you get that even in the
你得到的即使在
compiled version it's still a secure
编译版本仍然是安全的
execution so we get the bound checks
执行，所以我们得到了约束检查
there will be
将有
no no no random pointers pointing into
否否否随机指针指向
random memory locations with respective
具有各自的随机存储位置
without like if there are no errors or
没有错误或没有
bugs so normally you have the
错误，所以通常你有
precompiled JVM and then you execute
预编译的JVM，然后执行
your Java code dynamically on top of
您的Java代码动态地位于
that you load those classes at runtime
您在运行时加载这些类
and then you compile them just in time
然后您及时编译它们
so with the native images what you can
因此，使用本机图像可以
do you can get just one precompiled blob
你只能得到一个预编译的blob吗
and it happens like this we look at all
就像这样，我们看到了
the classes just literally all the
这些课程实际上就是
bytecode that will ever be executed
将会执行的字节码
inside your program and we statically
在您的程序中，我们会静态地
analyze that we find which code calls
分析我们发现哪些代码调用
which code and we we look at that and
哪些代码，我们看看
then we compile that we pre initialize
然后我们编译我们预初始化
some data we write it all into the
一些数据我们全部写入
binary format and then we just provide
二进制格式，然后我们只提供
some wrapper for the operating system to
操作系统的一些包装器
be able to execute that you can also
能够执行，你也可以
compile to assured library if you want
如果需要，编译为有保证的库
to but a native standalone executable
只能是本机独立可执行文件
might be more interesting so the
可能会更有趣，所以
important part here is the static
这里重要的是静态
analysis we look at the code and we
分析我们看一下代码，我们
analyze that statically that means that
进行静态分析意味着
we don't execute that actually right we
我们实际上并没有执行
just look at it and that poses certain
只要看看它，就可以确定
challenges and trade-offs namely
挑战与权衡
something's indeed our programs can
确实是我们的程序可以
happen dynamically for example you can
动态发生，例如，您可以
use reflection and we it's impossible to
使用反射，我们不可能
figure out the reflection calls
找出反思电话
statically not always possible it's not
静态上不可能总是不可能
generically universally possible so what
一般普遍可能
you need to do you need to provide some
你需要做的事你需要提供一些
hints some configuration saying that oh
提示一些配置，说哦
I've I'm gonna use this feature through
我要通过以下方式使用此功能
reflection I'm gonna patch those classes
反思我要修补那些课程
at runtime and then we can look at those
在运行时，然后我们可以看看那些
classes and we can put them into this
类，我们可以将它们放入
final executable tree provide the
最终的可执行树提供
configuration you need to write a JSON
您需要编写JSON的配置
file which could be a little bit
文件可能会有点
annoying to write JSON files we know we
讨厌写JSON文件，我们知道
know but it is possible
知道但有可能
so proxy configuration j'ni
所以代理配置j'ni
configuration reflection require some
配置反射需要一些
additional configuration from the
来自的其他配置
developer the good thing is as
开发人员的好处是
developers you are the sole owner of the
开发人员，您是该产品的唯一所有者
code that you're running right you can
您可以正确运行的代码
do anything whatever you can imagine you
做任何你想像不到的事
can do with the code
可以用代码做
that's the power of and the privilege of
那是...的力量和特权
being a developer so we can totally do
作为开发人员，所以我们可以完全做到
that since the ground viim 19 we have
自从地面viim 19我们
another another way of providing that
另一种提供方式
configuration we can run your java
配置我们可以运行你的java
program normally with the Java agent and
通常使用Java代理和
every time you use something through a
每次您通过
reflection it will gather that
反思会收集到
information and it will build those
信息，它将建立那些
configuration files for you right so you
适合您的配置文件，因此您
can use this assisted configuration run
可以使用此辅助配置运行
your tests run your application normally
您的测试正常运行您的应用程序
and then use those output files to give
然后使用这些输出文件
them to the compiler for building the
他们到编译器来构建
final image so configuring applications
最终映像，因此配置应用程序
became much easier you still need
变得更加轻松，您仍然需要
probably to exhaust all the code paths
可能会耗尽所有代码路径
but if you run your tests yet probably
但是如果您运行测试可能
you are in a much better shape than if
你的状态要比
you just try to gather those JSON files
您只是尝试收集这些JSON文件
and write them by hand
并用手写
the results the results are fairly
结果结果是相当
excellent the startup of those
优秀的那些
applications is in milliseconds right
申请时间以毫秒为单位
it's it can start in the typical web
它可以从典型的网络开始
service in under 20 milliseconds those
在不到20毫秒内
are the startup numbers for native
是本机的启动号
languages for go if you want to rewrite
要重写的语言
your systems and go for better startup
您的系统并获得更好的启动
maybe you shouldn't the runtime memory
也许您不应该运行时内存
overhead is also quite limited the thing
开销也相当有限的东西
is we don't need the machinery to load
是我们不需要机械来装载
dynamically additional classes there is
动态地有额外的类
no compiler in there so we don't need to
那里没有编译器，所以我们不需要
initialize all those data structures so
初始化所有这些数据结构，以便
we can run with literally just some
我们可以只使用一些
megabytes of RAM available and this is
可用的兆字节内存，这是
really good in certain environments if
在某些情况下真的很好
you disturb LS function the service or
您干扰LS功能的服务或
just all the scale and micro services
只是所有规模和微服务
this is the thing to look into right so
这是要注意的事情，所以
spring applications the most important
Spring 应用最重要
issue here is that currently out of the
这里的问题是，目前
box not all spring applications will
并非所有 Spring 应用都可以
work allegedly there is some support in
据称工作中有一些支持
the spring so currently for a year now
Spring ，所以现在一年了
since we announced that we want to get
自从我们宣布要获得
live with this we've been working fixing
我们一直在努力解决这个问题
issues and we're working and talking to
问题，我们正在努力并与之交谈
people engineers and and they made a lot
工程师，他们做了很多
of effort to make the framework code
编写框架代码的努力
more
更多
towards the native image generation and
面向本地图像生成和
the support the full support and the
支持，全力支持和
better support is coming in the upcoming
即将提供更好的支持
versions and we are looking forward to
版本，我们期待着
that
那
and I know the community is looking
我知道社区正在寻找
forward to that but currently if you try
转发到当前，但如果您尝试
just know that it's not fully there yet
只是知道还没有完全存在
you need to fiddle with configuration
您需要摆弄配置
you need to maybe use the certain
您可能需要使用某些
versions of the dravyam and string or
dravyam和字符串的版本，或
the starter files right so there are
入门文件正确，所以有
issues but the work is ongoing and the
问题，但工作仍在进行中，
progress has has been made so far and
到目前为止已经取得了进展，
the progress will be made further you
进步将使您更进一步
can check into that and you can you can
可以检查一下，你可以
try it you can also build other
试试看，你也可以建立其他
applications maybe be a little bit
应用程序可能会有点
easier but spring ones we are working on
我们正在努力工作的更轻松但 Spring 的工作
that right windows bits working java 11
正确的Windows位工作的Java 11
based versions are working in the works
基于版本的作品
when we have them we will announce them
当我们有他们时，我们将宣布他们
valium can do more things maybe a little
valium可以做更多的事情，也许有点
bit less interesting for Java developers
对于Java开发人员而言，有趣程度降低了
but certainly can deal them and just
但肯定可以解决他们
amount of time and don't want you to
时间量，不想你
remember the ground iam is a
记得地面iam是一个
high-performance Paul blood virtual
高性能保罗血液虚拟
machine embeddable in different
机器可嵌入不同
applications and you should try this and
应用程序，您应该尝试这样做
if you do anything of that if you're
如果你做任何事情，如果你
interested in that
对那个感兴趣
it's a project to look at thank you very
这是一个项目，非常感谢
much
许多
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]